<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Dragsbaek -- tech and health]]></title><description><![CDATA[A blog about technical mumbojumbo]]></description><link>https://blog.dragsbaek.tech</link><generator>RSS for Node</generator><lastBuildDate>Fri, 08 Feb 2019 20:52:00 GMT</lastBuildDate><item><title><![CDATA[Hello in the Kubernetes World]]></title><description><![CDATA[There are countless tutorials out there on how to get a basic kubernetes cluster up and running. In fact there are many more than you’d ever…]]></description><link>https://blog.dragsbaek.tech/hello-world/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://blog.dragsbaek.tech/hello-world/</guid><content:encoded>&lt;p&gt;There are countless tutorials out there on how to get a basic kubernetes cluster up and running. In fact there are many more than you’d ever need.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;But what’s missing out there, is some guidance on what to do when the cluster is up and running. The kubernetes community suffers from the same thing as the react community did in the beginning. Countless options, but no really opinionated starter-kits. You just had to mess around with things, until you were happy and had something that worked.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;At some point, someone decided to create &lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/facebook/create-react-app&quot;&gt;create-react-app&lt;/a&gt; and voila, you have this opinionated starter-kit with some sane defaults, that could scale well.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The purpose of this blog is to provide insights and analytics on getting up and running with kubernetes clusters, that have sane defaults - that would satisfy most security demands.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I want to write detailed and consise posts, that in details explain concepts that are important to understand, when running kubernetes in a micro-to-small or even a small-to-medium sized setup. I want to explore the available options and analyze the cost of each.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I also want to explore the “CI/CD” conumdrum and try to provide different options to allow for automating different popular methods of developing software, like GitOps and DevSecOps.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Hopefully it will be an interesting read for anyone that comes across my page. &lt;/p&gt;</content:encoded></item></channel></rss>